{
    "id": "b907bfedddfc4575b0c78296d3a94919",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The girls are playing in the garden. ……………….. look very happy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "They",
                "She",
                "We"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "584126306f664a43b17bd623ba481d29"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys are making a lot of noise. Please ask ……………… to be quiet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5417a417116d4bdb9e9a3283b4a9018f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is Rohan? I haven’t seen ………………. in several days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0c6399ab94984b59ba3390b4e447bc31"
        },
        {
            "question": "Raju complained to the teacher. ………………… bicycle had been stolen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "His",
                "He",
                "Him"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9ff18bc57fef48a8a68cdbf3562d7bce"
        },
        {
            "question": "My neighbors are some students. …………………. are very noisy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "They",
                "Their",
                "Them"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d96bd5d7da3240f3afce05bb8538cfbc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had invited all of ………………. friends but none of ……………….. turned up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "my, them",
                "me, they",
                "my, they"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f709fd1719e64008bedc24f56c448252"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never met James and I don’t know …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e1de659acfd149d48cc1508d41998747"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… are going to the movies. Do you want to come with …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "We, us",
                "We, we",
                "We, them"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "22172d2ecf8a4b0194f8608609a9e6f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie is a nice girl. Everyone likes ……………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "him",
                "her",
                "he"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6548293c4db94d4fb129459229e5190e"
        },
        {
            "question": "My daughters enjoy watching cartoon films. This CD is for ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "17a851f123b24073aa8dca708b51eb82"
        }
    ]
}